underwearexpert.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy – Help Center

At The Underwear Expert, we are 100% committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customers and site visitors. We would like to explain you in a simple and transparent way what personal data we gather about you and how do we process it. You share your personal information with us when you become a customer, when you register with our online services, subscribe for our newsletter or other marketing information, complete an online form, buy our products, open the Account or contact us through one of our channels.  
  
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. Personal data refers to any information that tells us something about you or that we can link to you. This includes your name, address, date of birth, account number, IP address or information about payments you’ve made from your bank account. By processing we mean everything we can do with this data such as collecting it, recording, storing, adjusting, organizing, using, disclosing, transferring or deleting.  
  
Topics:

  * Information Collection
  * Information Usage
  * Information Security
  * Sharing of Information
  * Cookie Policy
  * COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
  * CAN SPAM Act
  * European Economic Area - General Data Protection Regulation
  * Changes and Updates
  * Contacting Us

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

When you use The Underwear Expert services, we may ask you to provide certain personal information to obtain our products or use our services.  For example, we may ask for information when you register to create an account, update your information, sign up for a membership or subscription, use certain features, access, purchase products or services, enter into sweepstakes or other promotions, register or participate in a competition, fill out a survey, request customer support, or otherwise communicate with us.  We (or our service providers or business partners) may collect information that relates to you, including personal information **,** such as your name, e-mail address, telephone number, phone number, mailing address, date of birth, gender, and demographic information.   **Information You Provide When You Participate in an Online Survey or Other Research**. We may also collect information you provide us in connection with participating in an online survey or as a research panel participant.  This may include, but may not be limited to, information about your shopping habits, lifestyle preferences, interests and hobbies, health, physical or behavioral characteristics, or other demographic information, as well as photos, videos, and other user-generated content.  

**Information You Provide When You Make a Purchase**. If you make a purchase from us, you will be required to provide a credit/debit card number and related financial information (such as CVV, expiration date, and billing address), or other payment information (such as via PayPal or Apple Pay), depending on the form of payment you choose.     
 **  
Information You Provide about a Third Party**. You may decide to provide us with another person's information (such as name, email, address, or phone number) so that we may recommend or send products or services to such person, or so that we may facilitate your communication with other people. Local law may require you to seek the consent of your contacts to provide their personal information to The Underwear Expert (or in connection with using The Underwear Expert services), which may in turn use that information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Where required by law, we will obtain the required consent from the person whose information you provided to us. **Information You Provide Through Social Media**. You may also be given the option to link to your Facebook or other social media accounts through The Underwear Expert services. When you do, we may automatically receive certain information from you based upon your privacy settings on those sites. This may include, but may not be limited to, name, user name, demographic information, updated address or contact information, location, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and online activity. **Information Collected Automatically.** Whenever you visit or interact with The Underwear Expert, The Underwear Expert, as well as any third-party advertisers and/or service providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect information about your online activity. This information may be collected in the following ways: **Usage Information.**   We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, mobile analytics software, log files, or other technologies to collect certain information about your online activity, and interactions with our emails, online and mobile advertisements, and to allow us to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables The Underwear Expert to improve our services and provide you with more relevant content and advertising offered by The Underwear Expert. **Geolocation Information.** We may collect information about the location of your Device when you access or use The Underwear Expert services. In addition, if you choose to turn on your Bluetooth, Wi-Fi or other geolocation functionality when you use our mobile applications, we may collect and use your geolocation information. **Third Party Service Providers**. We may use third party service providers to support The Underwear Expert services.  Some of these service providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or other technologies to receive, collect, and store information on our behalf. **Third Party Analytic Technologies.** We may use third parties’ analytics and tracking tools, such as Google Analytics, Facebook Custom Audience and others, to help us track, segment and analyze usage of the The Underwear Expert, and to help us or those third parties serve more targeted advertising to you on the The Underwear Expert services and across the Internet. These tools may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, Flash cookies, or other technologies to collect and store non-personal information. They may also combine information they collect from your interaction with the The Underwear Expert services with information they collect from other sources. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies.

**How long do we keep your personal data.** We are only allowed to keep your personal data for as long as it is necessary for the purpose we initially required it. After this we look for feasible solutions like archiving it. The appropriate retention periods for each category of data are based on the requirements of applicable data protection laws and the purpose for which the information is collected and used, taking into account legal and regulatory requirements to retain the information for a minimum period, limitation periods for taking legal action, good practice and Underwear Expert business purposes.

**INFORMATION USAGE**

We may use the information about you in a variety of ways:  

**For Customer Service and Transaction Purposes, such as to:**

  * respond to your questions or requests and provide customer service;
  * manage your account and registration;
  * troubleshoot issues, bugs or defects related to your account or activities;
  * validate, confirm, verify, deliver, and track your order (including to arrange for shipping, handle returns and refunds, and contact you about your orders, including by telephone), and send you related information, coupons, products or samples;
  * verify your identity or communicate with you about your activities with respect to The Underwear Expert services;
  * to use and disclose your credit, debit or payment card or other financial information only to process payments and prevent fraud;
  * develop new products or services and to enhance current products and services;
  * protect the security or integrity of The Underwear Expert services and our business, such as by protecting against and preventing fraud, unauthorized transactions, claims and other liabilities, and managing risk exposure, including by identifying potential hackers and other unauthorized users; and
  * for other purposes as disclosed at the time you provide your personal information or otherwise with your consent.

**For Advertising Customization and Analytics Purposes, such as to:**

  * perform market research, understand the effectiveness of our competition or promotions and The Underwear Expert services analytics and operations;
  * personalize and improve The Underwear Expert services and our products, services, offers and advertising  made available on or outside The Underwear Expert services (including on other sites/ applications that you visit).  For example, we may provide personalized or localized content, recommendations, features, and provide content or features that match your interests and preferences;
  * provide you with customized content, advertisements, offers and promotions offered by The Underwear Expert or on behalf of our partners and affiliates, and provide news and other information we think will be of interest to you on The Underwear Expert services, in emails and across third-party websites;
  * link or combine with information we receive from others to help understand your needs, use for interest-based or targeted advertising or re-targeting on your computers or other devices, and to provide you with better service; and
  * communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners (e.g., through Facebook Custom Audience, Google Customer Match, etc.) for The Underwear Expert marketing and promotional purposes via emails, notifications, or other messages, consistent with any permissions you may have communicated to us.

Our general attitude is that data that we process for any other reason is anonymized or we remove as much of the personal information as possible.

**INFORMATION SECURITY  
** **  
** **How do we protect your information?** Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

**Third-party disclosure.** We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

**Third-party links.** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google.** Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

  *       Remarketing with Google AdSense
  *       Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  *       Demographics and Interests Reporting
  *       DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out.** Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**Legal Disclosures.** Where necessary, or for the reasons set out in this policy, personal information may also be shared with regulatory authorities, courts, tribunals, government agencies and law enforcement agencies.  While it is unlikely, we may be required to disclose your information to comply with legal or regulatory requirements. We will use reasonable endeavors to notify you before we do this, unless we are legally restricted from doing so.

**Anonymous Non-Personal Information.** Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act.** CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following.** Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above. You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page. You can change your personal information by logging in to your account.  

**Which countries we transfer your personal information to.** In order to provide our services, your personal data may be transferred to the USA, Countries outside the USA, including the European Economic Area (the “EEA”).  The level of information protection in countries outside the EEA may be less than that offered within the EEA. Where this is the case, we will implement appropriate measures to ensure that your personal information remains protected and secure in accordance with applicable data protection laws.  EU standard contractual clauses are in place between Underwear Expert and entities that share and process personal data. Where our third party service providers process personal data outside the EEA in the course of providing services to us, our written agreement with them will include appropriate measures, usually standard contractual clauses.

**COOKIE POLICY**

**Do we use 'cookies'?** Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use technical cookies, tracking cookies and third-party cookies. 

**We use cookies to:**

  *       Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  *       Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  *       Keep track of advertisements.
  *       Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**Your consent for using cookies.** By accessing our site, you consent to our use of cookies. If you are located in the EU, you will receive a popup notice on the website. We also uses cookies for which we do not require your consent as they are cookies necessary to render you our services. Without them the services that you have asked for cannot be provided.

**If you disable cookies in your browser.** If you disable cookies, some features will be disabled such as ecommerce functionality and other site functionality. This will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

**What about your privacy?** The cookies used by us do not allow a person to be identified individually. Cookies do not contain any personal information so it cannot link you as a person to any name or surname. Only the IT system on which the cookie is stored can be identified via its IP address.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act).** When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**CAN SPAM Act.**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

  *       Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  *       Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  *       Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  *       Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

  *       Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  *       Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  *       Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  *       Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  *       Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  *       Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you do so by clicking the link on the bottom of each email** and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**GDPR (European Economic Area Countries Only)**

**General Data Protection Regulation refers to specific rights of people in the European Economic Area with respect to how we respect personal data.  
** **  
**In accordance with General Data Protection Regulation you have the:

  * **Right to access information** \- You have the right to ask us for an overview of your personal data that we process.
  * **Right to data portability** \- You have the right to ask us to transfer your personal data directly to you or to another entity. This applies to personal data we process by automated means and with your consent or on the basis of a contract with you. We will transfer your personal data where it is technically feasible.
  * **Right to erasure** \- You may ask us to erase your personal data if we no longer need it for its original purpose, you object to us processing your data for our own legitimate interests or for personalised commercial messages, you withdraw your consent for processing your data, we unlawfully process your personal data, or a law of the European Union or a member state of the European Union requires us to erase your personal data. 
  * **Right to object to processing** \- You can object to us using your personal data for its own legitimate interests. We will consider your objection and whether processing your information has any undue impact on you that requires us to stop doing so. You can also object to receiving personalized commercial messages from us. When you become an Underwear Expert customer we may ask you whether you want to receive personalised offers. Should you later change your mind, you can choose to opt out of receiving these messages by using the “unsubscribe” link located at the bottom of each marketing email. You cannot object to us processing your personal data if we are legally required to do so e.g. if we are obliged to fulfil a contract with you such as shipping an order. 
  * **Right to object to automated decisions** \- We sometimes use IT systems to make automated decisions based on your personal information if this is necessary to fulfil a contract with you or if you gave us consent to do so. You have the right to object to such automated decisions and ask for an actual person to make the decision instead.
  * **Right to rectification** \- If your personal data is incorrect, you have the right ask us to rectify it. If we shared data about you with a third party, it is our obligation to notify this change to the third party.
  * **Right to restrict processing** \- You have the right to ask us to restrict using your personal data if in your opinion the information is inaccurate, we are processing the data unlawfully, you have objected to us processing your data for our own legitimate interests.
  * **Right to complain** \- Should you not be satisfied with the way we have responded to your concerns you have the right to submit a complaint to us. If you are still unhappy with our reaction to your complaint, you can also contact the data protection authority in your country.

Your data controller is: The Underwear Expert Inc.

**CHANGES AND UPDATES.**

We may amend this Privacy Statement to remain compliant with any changes in law and/or to reflect how our business processes personal data. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. If you do not agree or consent to these updates or changes, do not continue to use The Underwear Expert services. 

In addition to this Privacy Policy, there may be specific campaigns or promotions which will be governed by additional privacy terms or policies. 

**Fair Information Practices.** The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur. We will notify you via email within 7 business days and we will notify all users via in-site within 7 business days.

**CONTACTING US.**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, or to submit a complaint, you may contact us using the information below. We aim to respond to your request as quickly as possible. In some instances this could take up to one month (if legally allowed). Should we require more time to complete your request, we will let you know how much longer we need and provide reasons for the delay.

The Underwear Expert Inc.  
134 N. 4th Street  
2nd Floor  
Brooklyn, NY 11249  
United States

Email: [help @ underwearexpert.com](mailto:help@underwearexpert.com) or use the contact us link below.  
Phone: +1 646-553-4710

This policy was last modified on **May 19,  2018**
